Guide to the Physical Plant, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Physical Plant, Yale University, records
1971-1976
RU 195
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of files of the Yale Physical Plant documenting projects and accounts.
Yale University. Physical Plant
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files of the Yale Physical Plant documenting projects and accounts.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
College buildings -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Maintenance and repair; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Physical Plant
- Building project records, circa 1971-1976; Accession 1986-A-090
  - Projects, 1973-76
    - Pierson-Sage Parking Structure (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Renovations (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Yale Repertory Theater (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
    - Alterations (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - School of Organization andManagement 6852-39-60431 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Old Campus Renovation (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Engineering Services (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Mellon Project - General Construction (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
    - Mellon Project - Architecture (Box 1, Folder 14-17)
    - Laboratory for Surgery, Obstetrics, and Gynecology, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Yale Indoor Tennis Facility (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Undergraduate Residential Housing (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - American Arts Center (lecture hall addition to Art Gallery 1975-1976) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Mabel Grady Garvan Gallery (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Art and Architecture Renovation, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Architect and Contractor accounts, 1973-1975
    - Estate of Louis I. Kahn-Yale Center for British Art (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
    - Air Balancing Service Company (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Baldwin Stewart (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Bartels Constructions (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Clarence Blair Associates (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - James E. Brennan Company, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - BUCK Routh (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Chapman (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Civitello (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Cybernetics (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Edison Price Lighting (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - George Ellis Company (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Elmore Associates (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Otto Hoeptner and Sons (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Homecraft Drapery and Upholstery Corporation (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - M. Meyers (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - New Haven Testing (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Pfisterer, Tor (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Reproductions United (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Taylor Mechanical Services, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - TRIO Industries (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - James Ursini Company (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Van Zelon (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - John Arthur Weick, Architect (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Paul S. Yoder, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - York Research Corporation (Box 2, Folder 51)